The world fell grey A missing piece
A quiet, slow and sad release
A chapter closed A best friend gone Just trying
to find a way to carry
on The days were long, the colors faded A little
lost and worn and jaded
Then you walked in and caught
my eye We leave the dull community college sky
You talk of dreams and taking flight
Of leaving all the dark for light
You say you see the real me there
A kindred soul beyond compare
It feels so fast. It feels so right.
A sudden stop in my dark night.
You fill the void. You bridge the gap. A perfect
escape.
I see a new light in your lonely room
But there's a shadow chasing after you
You see a fast car on an open road I see a heavy,
heavy load
And for the first time in a long, long while
And you're a new light in a lonely room
Chasing away the coming gloom
You're a fast car on an open road Lifting off a
heavy load
And for the first time in a long, long while, a new
life. Oh, my dear brother, please be smart.
This new life's gonna break your heart. It's
gonna break your heart.